RG 002:025, Executive and Legislative Nominations Committee
Connecticut State Library
Executive and Legislative Nominations Committee records
1985-2005
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly. Executive and Legislative Nominations Committee
3.75 cubic feet
Executive and Legislative Nominations Committee meeting and nomination files.
RG002_025_NOM
Multiple
Scope and Content
Executive and Legislative Nominations Committee meeting and nomination files.
Arrangement
Arranged by accession.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Executive and Legislative Nominations Committee
Subjects:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Executive and Legislative Nominations Committee -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut -- Officials and employees -- Selection and appointment; Nominations for office -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Agendas; Membership lists; Minutes
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Accession T001598, 1985-1991
  - Meeting minutes of Joint Committee, 1985 January - May (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes, 1986 March 26 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes and agenda, 1987 January - May (Box 1)
  - Public hearings - agendas, attendance, and tape notes, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative action plan correspondence to commissioners, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Membership, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1988 February - April (Box 1)
  - Public hearings schedules and agendas, 1988 February - April (Box 1)
  - Membership, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Nominations list, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1989 January - April (Box 1)
  - Public hearings agendas and attendance sheets, 1989 February - May (Box 1)
  - Membership, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Nominations list, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Meeting agendas, 1990 January - April (Box 1)
  - Public hearings agendas and attendance sheets, 1990 February - May (Box 1)
  - Membership, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Nominations list, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes, 1991 January 23 (Box 1)
- Accession 1993-148, 1987-1989
  - Status book, 1987 January 29 - February 27 (Box 1)
  - Status book, 1987 March 19 - June 3 (Box 2)
  - Hearing transcripts, 1988 February - April (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Hearing transcripts, 1989 January - June (Box 3)
- Accession 1999-153, 1991
  - Meeting minutes and agendas, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Reports, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Committee Members, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Minutes, 1991 (Box 1)
- Accession 2008-012, 2005
  - Nominee files, 2005
    - A-O (Box 1)
    - P-Z (Box 2)